http://rapindustry.com/privacy

KEEP UP TO DATE: Coronavirus (COVID-19)
0
Def Jam looking for a new CEO / Rosenberg steps down.
0
ON DECK: Chance The Rapper, Common, Lil Wayne, Jennifer Hudson & more for NBA All-Star Game/ Kobe Tribute.
0
Ice Cube to Star in True-Life Boxing Tale ‘Flint Strong’
February 5, 2020
0
0
Cube’s Kid – O’Shea Jackson Jr. On Deck in Apple’s Basketball Drama ‘Swagger’
February 5, 2020
0
0
Rihanna to Receive President’s Award at 51st NAACP Image Awards
February 5, 2020
0
0
Nicki Minaj’s brother sentenced to 25 years to life in prison
January 27, 2020
0
0
Eminem Scores Historic 10th No. 1 Album / 1st Week Album Sales Record
January 27, 2020
0
0
Grammys Winners 2020 – Hip-Hop/ R&b, Reggae list.
0
Is the Fix In? Recent Grammy Boss gives her take.
January 23, 2020
0
0
Latest News
KEEP UP TO DATE: Coronavirus (COVID-19)
-Privacy Statement
Thank you for visiting RAPINDUSTRY.COM. Your privacy is important to us.
RAPINDUSTRY.COM has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the website www.rapindustry.com.
We at Rapindustry.com are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) you share with us.
Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. In general, you can visit Rapindustry.com’s web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself.
Rapindustry.com strives to comply with all applicable laws around the globe that are designed to protect your privacy. Although legal requirements may vary from country to country, Rapindustry.com intends to adhere to the principles set forth in this Online Privacy Policy even if, in connection with the above, we transfer your Personal Information from your country to countries that may not require an “adequate” level of protection for your Personal Information. In other words, our goal is to provide protection for your Personal Information no matter where that Personal Information is collected, transferred, or retained.
Links to Sites Outside of Rapindustry.com
The Site contain links to other websites. Please note that third parties may collect information about you, through cookies or other technologies, when you link to their websites through our Site. You acknowledge that we do not monitor or control the information collection or privacy practices of these or any other third parties, and are not responsible for their practices or the content of their websites. You should review the privacy policies of such third parties to understand how they collect and use information.
Customer Order Information
Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor’s contact information (like their email address), unique identifiers, financial information (like their account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders, information about our company, and promotional material from some of our partners to our customers. The customer’s contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary and shared with other companies who may want to contact our visitors. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services.Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor’s experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is rarely shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.
Surveys and Questionnaires
Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like their email address), unique identifiers, and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or spending levels). We use contact data from our surveys to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The customer’s contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor’s experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is rarely shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.
Contests and Games
We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address), unique identifiers, and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or spending level on music). We use contact data from our contests to send users information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners and affiliates. The customer’s contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor’s experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is rarely shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.
Under 18
If you are under 18 years of age, you should not provide any personally identifiable information on this site without the knowledge and permission of your parent or guardian. There are certain web pages within our website that require users to be at least 18 years of age; This may mean that you will be unable to participate in some activities on the site without parent or guardian’s consent..
How We Use the Information
We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, and to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you. We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when you have won one of our contests or when we make changes to our subscriber agreements, and also to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter. We use the information that you provide about others to enable us to send them your gifts or cards. From time to time, we also may use this information to offer our products, programs, or services to them. Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Notice.
Our Commitment to Security
Our servers have in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online. But because no security system is impenetrable, we cannot guarantee the security of our servers.
How You Can Opt- Out
This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.
You can send request to the following email: webmaster@rapindustry.com
How You Can Update or Correct Information
For instructions on how you can UPDATE the personally identifiable information that this site has collected about you online, or how to correct factual errors in such information, this site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided.
You can send request to the following email: webmaster@rapindustry.com.
To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
Your Consent
By using this Web site, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy and to Rapindustry.com’s processing of Personal Information for the purposes given above as well as those explained where Rapindustry.com collects Personal Information on the Web. Should the Online Privacy Policy change, we intend to take every reasonable step to ensure that these changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on our web site for a reasonable period of time.
Home
© 2018 RAPINDUSTRY.COM . All right reserved.
